[{"question": " how could someone get a hold of your credit card number?", "answer": " i have no idea. but look how much they spent!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " monica, would you calm down? the credit card people said that you only have to pay for the stuff that you bought.", "answer": " i know. it's just such reckless spending.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " i think when someone steals your credit card, they've kind of already thrown caution to the wind.", "answer": " wow, what a geek. they spent $69.95 on a wonder mop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " that's me.", "answer": " oh! the yuk! ross, he's doing it again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " marcel, stop humping the lamp! stop humping! now marcel, come back-  come here, marcel-", "answer": " oh no, not in my room! i'll get him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " ross, you've got to do something about the humping.", "answer": " what? it's, it's just a phase.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " well, that's what we said about joey...", "answer": " would you all relax? it's not that big a deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  stop it! marcel! bad monkey!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh, monica. you are not still going over that thing.", "answer": " this woman's living my life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " she's living my life, and she's doing it better than me! look at this, look. she buys tickets for plays that i wanna see. she, she buys clothes from stores that i'm intimidated by the sales people. she spent three hundred dollars on art supplies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " you're not an artist.", "answer": " yeah, well i might be if i had the supplies! i mean, i could do all this stuff. only i don't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh, monica, c'mon, you do cool things.", "answer": " oh really? okay, let's compare, shall we.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  oh, it's so late for 'shall we'...", "answer": " do i go horseback riding in the park? do i take classes at the new school?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  nooo...", "answer": " this is so unfair! she's got everything i want, and she doesn't have my mother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " how about joey... pepponi?", "answer": " no, still too ethnic. my agent thinks i should have a name that's more neutral.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " plus, y'know, i think it should be joe. y'know, joey makes me sound like i'm, i dunno, this big.  which i'm not.", "answer": " joe...joe...joe...stalin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " stalin...stalin...do i know that name? it sounds familiar.", "answer": " well, it does not ring a bell with me...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  joe stalin. y'know, that's pretty good.", "answer": " might wanna try joseph.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " joseph stalin. i think you'd remember that!", "answer": " oh yes! bye bye birdie, starring joseph stalin. joseph stalin is the fiddler on the roof.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hi.  hi, uh, yes, this is monica geller. um, i believe i'm taking some classes with you and i was wondering what they were.", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  alright, great. thanks a lot.  i'm going to tap class.", "answer": " what, what, so that you can dance with the woman that stole your credit card?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " this woman's got my life, i should get to see who she is.", "answer": " go to the post office! i'm sure her picture's up! ...okay, monica, y'know what, honey, you're kinda losing it here! i mean, this is really becoming like a weird obsession thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " what d'you think?", "answer": " lotsa things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " may i help you?", "answer": " oh, no thanks, we're just here to observe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " you don't observe a dance class. you dance a dance class. spare shoes are over there.", "answer": " what does she mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " okay, d'y'see anybody you think could be me?", "answer": "  people! last time there were some empty yoghurt containers lying around after class. let's not have that happen again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " okay, i'm not getting this!", "answer": "  i'm totally getting it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " what? you just click when they click.", "answer": " alright people, now everyone grab a partner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " okay. and, my, dead, mother, says, you, are, it. i'm with rachel.", "answer": " great. it's gym class all over again. phoebe and rachel: aww.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " well that's all right, you can come up to the front and dance with me.", "answer": " why don't i just take off my clothes and have a nightmare.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " it's okay, it's okay, i'm here, i'm here. sorry i'm late, okay, here i am. who's the new tense girl?", "answer": " she's your partner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hi. i'm monica.", "answer": " oh. monica! ...hi. i'm mo- ...nana. woman : monana?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yeah. it's dutch.", "answer": " you're kidding! i-i spent three years in amsterdam.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " um, pennsylvania dutch.", "answer": " and we're dancing. a-five, six, seven, eight...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  hi. chandler and joey: hey.", "answer": " where've you been?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " at the vet.", "answer": " she's not gonna make you wear one of those big plastic cones, is she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " she says marcel's humping thing's not a phase. apparently he's reached sexual maturity.", "answer": "  hey! he beat ya.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " she says as time goes on, he's gonna start getting agressive and violent.", "answer": " so what does this mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " i can't believe it, ross. this sucks!", "answer": " i don't get it, i mean, you just got him. how can he be an adult already?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i know. i know. i mean, one day, he's this little thing, and before you know it, he's this little thing i can't get off my leg.", "answer": " isn't there any way you can keep him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no, no. the vet says unless he's in a place where he has regular access to some... monkey lovin', he's just gonna get vicious. i've just gotta get him into a zoo.", "answer": " how do you get a monkey into a zoo?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i know that one! ...no, that's popes into a volkswagen.", "answer": " well, we're applying to a lot of them. naturally our first choice would be one of the bigger state zoos, y'know, like, uh, san diego... right? but that might just be a pipe dream, because, y'know, he's out of state. uh, my vet, uh, knows someone at miami, so that's a possibility.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hey. we found her, we found the girl.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " did you call the cops?", "answer": " nope. we took her to lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " ah. your own brand of vigilante justice.", "answer": " what?! are you insane? this woman stole from you. she stole. she's a stealer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " y'know what? after you're with this woman for like ten minutes, you forget all that. i mean, she is this astounding person, with this- with this amazing spirit.", "answer": " yeah, which she probably stole from some cheerleader.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " ...take off their hats!", "answer": " popes in a volkswagen! ...i love that joke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no way. no way did you do this.", "answer": " monana was very brave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " it was so wild. we told them we were the gunnersens in room six fifteen. only to find out the boston celtics had taken over the entire sixth floor!", "answer": " so once they caught on to the fact that we're, y'know, short and have breasts...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " ...they threw us out! i was thrown out of a hotel! me!", "answer": " go monana! well, you ladies are not the only ones living the dream. i get to go pour coffee for people i don't know. don't wait up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh, by the way, tomorrow we're auditioning for a broadway show.", "answer": " 'scuse me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " there's an open call for cats. i'm thinking we go down there, sing memories and make complete fools of ourselves. whaddya say?", "answer": " nononononono. think who you're dealing with here. i mean, i'm not like you. i-i can't even stand in front of a tap class.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " well, that's just probably 'cause of your amish background.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " well, you're pennsylvania dutch, right?", "answer": " right. till i bought a blow dryer, then i was shunned.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i-i used to be just like you. and then one day i saw a movie that changed my life. did you ever see dead poets' society?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i thought that movie was so incredibly... boring. i mean, that thing at the end where the kid kills himself because he can't be in the play? what was that?! it's like, kid, wait a year, leave home, do some community theatre. i walked out of there and i thought, 'now, that's two hours of my life that i'm never getting back'. and that thought scared me more than all the other crap i was afraid to do.", "answer": " wow. then i would definitely not recommend mrs. doubtfire.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": "  oh god.  we didn't get into scranton.  that was like our safety zoo. they take like dogs and cows. see? i don't know who this is harder on, me or him.", "answer": " i'd say that chair's taking the brunt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " marcel! marcel! marcel, no! good boy. see, how can nobody want him?", "answer": " oh, somebody will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " you know there already is a joseph stalin?", "answer": " you're kidding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " apparently he was this russian dictator who slaughtered all these people. you'd think you would've known that!", "answer": " y'know, you'd think i would've.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " phoebe. whaddyou think a good stage name for me would be?", "answer": " ...flame boy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " where exactly is your zoo?", "answer": " well, it's technically not a zoo per se, it's more of an interactive wildlife experience. let me ask you some questions about, is it, uh, marcel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " does he, uh, fight with other animals?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " nono, he's, he's very docile.", "answer": " even if he were... cornered?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " well i, i don't know. why?", "answer": " uh, how is he at handling small objects?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " he can hold a banana, if that's whatcha mean...", "answer": " how about a hammer, or a small blade?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " why- why- why would he need a blade?", "answer": " well, if he's up against a jungle cat or an animal with horns, you've got to give the little guy something. otherwise it's just cruel.  chandler and joey: he- he- he got in, he- he got in to san diego.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " we, we come back from our walk and the- the phone was ringing-", "answer": " -he's in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " he's in! oh, did you hear that, marcel? san diego. san diego!", "answer": " you're making a big mistake here. i mean, san diego's all well and good, but if you give him to me, i'll start him off against a blind rabbit and give you twenty percent of the gains.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " yo- hooo!", "answer": " where the hell've you been?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " monica and i just crashed an embassy party.", "answer": " are you drunk?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " noooo!  i'm lying. i am so drunk.", "answer": " oh god, oh. great, monica, y'know what, you could've called, i have been up here, i've been worried...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " monica? monica!", "answer": " water rules!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " yes, yes, it does. okay, look, the restaurant called, they wanna know if you're gonna be showing up for work?", "answer": " nope. going to the big apple circus today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay monica, what are you doing? you're gonna lose your job! this is not you!", "answer": " no, it is me! y'know, i'm not just the person who needs to fluff the pillows and pay the bills as soon as they come in! y'know, when i'm with her, i am so much more than that. i'm- i'm monana!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hello? yes, she is, hold on a second, please. monana, it's for you, the credit card people.", "answer": " helloooo? yeah. oh my god. thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " they've arrested monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " how are you?", "answer": " i'm not too bad. fortunately, blue's my colour. how- how did you know i was here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " because... i'm monica geller. it was my credit card you were using.", "answer": " that i was not expecting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i want you to know, it wasn't me who turned you in.", "answer": " oh. thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no, thank you! you have given me so much! i mean, if it wasn't for you, i would never have gotten to sing memories on the stage at the wintergarden theatre!", "answer": " well, actually, you only got to sing 'memo-'.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " i just can't believe you're in here. i mean, what am i gonna do without you? who's gonna crash the embassy parties with me? who's gonna take me to the big apple circus?", "answer": " monica, i started my day by peeing in front of twenty-five other women, and you're worried about who's gonna take you to the big apple circus?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " well, not... worried, just... wondering.", "answer": " there's nothing to wonder about, monica. you're gonna go back to being exactly who you were, because that's who you are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " not necessarily...", "answer": " yes necessarily! i mean, i dunno what it is, maybe it's the amish thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " um, i'm not actually amish.", "answer": " really? then why are you like that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " you by the door. in or out?", "answer": " in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " you in the back, you're getting it all wrong!", "answer": " yeah, but at least i'm doing it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " this is the final boarding call for flight 67 to san diego, boarding at gate 42a.", "answer": " okay. goodbye, little monkey guy. alright, i wrote you this poem. okay, but don't eat it 'till you get on the 'plane.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " aww. thank you, aunt phoebe.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " okay, bye, champ. now, i know there's gonna be a lot of babes in san diego, but remember, there's also a lot to learn.", "answer": " i dunno what to say, ross. uh, it's a monkey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " just, just say what you feel.", "answer": " marcel, i'm hungry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " that was good.", "answer": "  marcel, this is for you. it's, uh, just, y'know, something to, um, do on the 'plane.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " uh, if you guys don't mind, i'd like to take a moment, just me and him.", "answer": " oh, sure. sure, absolutely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " hi, uh, i'll be reading for the role of mercutio. casting director #2: name?", "answer": " holden mcgroin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}]